Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/john-alexis-villabeto-a54219291 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Thorough Research
Data Collection
Data Processing

John Alexis Villabeto

E-Commerce Warehouse Staff @ Hatasu Philippines Taytay, Calabarzon, Philippines

Summary

My name is John Alexis Villabeto, I am a Freelancer with not much yet professional

experience. But, If you give me opportunities in this field. I can assure you that I will

do my best to meet your standard of work. I'm interested in this opportunity

because I want to know more about myself, strength and weaknesses to develop

and hone my knowledge and skills more. I want to support myself and my future self

through this.

The last job I had was Data Processor in Multilingual Department Speaking Team in

CCK City Network Inc. that has been operating for 17th years. In CCK all Data

Processor score tests of the Japanese students from elementary to college level,

covering various subjects. We process their development and record the results on

our quota sheet.

Also I am also a self-motivated problem-solver and a team player. I Hope that I can work for you.

Best regards.

Freelancer

Yours sincerely, Ja. Villabeto

Experience

Hatasu Philippines
E-Commerce Warehouse Staff
September 2024 - Present (4 months)

CCK City Network, Inc.
Data Processor
December 2023 - October 2024 (11 months)
Pasig, National Capital Region, Philippines

Education

ACLC College

Bachelor of Science - BS, Information System · (May 2020 - August 2024)

STI College

Senior High School, Science, Technology, Engineering, Mathematics · (May 2017 - May 2019)